If cotton hair is true, could everything they said be true as well?
If I can just get back to Kokoyashi Village, I'm sure I could figure it all out.
But without a decent ship, how am I gonna get there?
And I'm on the Grand Line of all places.
According to this math, it's impossible to sail directly from this sea to the East Blue.
Wait! What's that?!
You're the captain?!
Aw, man! That was a lucky break. If I hadn't gotten my memory back,
I would've been stuck eye-eyeing Captain Usopp forever.
Shut your mouth! I'm never gonna believe it!
No matter what anyone says, I know that I'm the Great Captain Usopp!
I have an army of 8,000 pirates who obey my every command!
That's the Usopp I know through and through!
But you're not the captain. You're Usopp, the sniper of the Straw Hat Pirates!
Crap! The tables have turned against me.
This guy's a monster just like me, and yet he's the captain?
Hey, Chopper!
Keep away!
Aw, come on! How long are you gonna act like that?
Let's play like we always do!
So, I'm the ship's doctor, and this is something I always do?
Yeah! You do it every time we have a party! It's like your thing!
Come on, Chopper!
That rubber monkey said he got his memories back, yet he's acting just as much of an idiot as before.
Huh.
That's right. The captain never ever changes, no matter what happens to him.
Even if I am a pirate, I'm nothing compared to these freaks of nature.
I'd never survive sailing with the likes of them. How did I get myself into this mess?
Now it's clear what happened. Everyone didn't miraculously lose their memories overnight.
They were stolen, and so the obvious culprit is...
The only person we all remember, that brat.
What would that freaky kid want with our memories anyway?
Beats me.
Wait a sec!
We have to get Nami and Zoro back! Come on! Let's go!
You're right, but we should wait until morning.
Why can't we go right now?
Searching for two people on an unknown island in the middle of the night is a recipe for disaster.
Oh. Guess you got a point.
Let's get some rest, and then we'll begin our search when the sun comes up.
I don't think that boy will be back tonight. We gave him a lot of trouble.
He'll think twice before showing up here again.
Hmm. Right! It's settled! We'll rest up and start the search first thing in the morning!
Hold on a sec. I'm all for bringing that lovely lady Nami back, but not that Zoro guy.
He can just stay gone for all I care.
I agree! If you two want to go look for him, you can do it on your own!
I, uh, I'm not sure.
What the? What are you saying?
We're saying why look for Zoro.
He's a pirate hunter, remember? Why should we go through all the trouble of chasing down a guy like that?
Isn't it obvious? Because he's our friend.
Just because you said it doesn't mean it's true. Come on.
That guy sure didn't act like he was our friend. Surely you noticed that.
The way he left is proof enough for me.
Usopp is the sniper, Sanji is the cook, Chopper is the doctor, Robin is the archaeologist, Nami is the navigator, and Zoro is the swordsman.
We are the Straw Hat Pirates, and we don't leave any man behind!
Then we'll have to get Mr. Swordsman's memory back.
No problem! All I have to do is kick that brat's butt again! That's how I got mine back! Sound good, Chopper?
Well, it looks like tomorrow's gonna be a really busy day.
Alright, let's all get some sleep while we can!
The key to unraveling this mystery is somewhere on that island.
It seems that I underestimated you, Monkey D. Luffy. You're a formidable enemy.
Still, you won't stop me from making my wish come true.
But in order to do so, I'll need an ally.
An ally.
An ally like a certain skilled swordsman.
That's right. He's different than he was yesterday.
This man is Pirate Hunter Zoro. If I try to approach him, things could go bad quickly.
Okay, then. I'll cut my losses for tonight. There'll be other chances soon, anyway.
Oh, yes. And when that time comes, your work will truly begin.
It is said that fish from around the world gathered together in the All Blue.
I'll cut my losses for tonight.
There'll be other chances soon, anyway.
Oh, yes.
And when that time comes, your work will truly begin.
It is said that fish from around the world
gathered together in the all-blue
have dreamed of reaching that sea.
Why'd you help me?
It doesn't make sense to sacrifice so much for me,
you old fool!
Tell me!
Because for my entire life,
I've had the same dream as you.
A restaurant?
I was thinking that if I make it out of this mess alive,
I'd like to build a restaurant as my final purpose.
Great!
And I'll even help you do it!
So don't die, okay?
A weak little brat like you
couldn't be much good for anything.
Then I'll become strong!
That annoying old geezer saved my life.
There's no way I would have ever left him.
So why?
What the hell happened to me?
Pepper, carrot, onion.
I wonder what happened to the Usopp pirates.
It's go time, brave Usopp pirates!
We do have a village that we need to protect!
So what adventure are you going to tell me about today?
Well, let's see.
Oh, I know.
What about the story of me fighting a giant goldfish at the South Pole when I was only five years old?
Goldfish?
A giant goldfish!
What first astounded me was the immense size of its poop!
It was so big that when I landed on it, I thought it was solid ground!
Usopp!
I always dreamed of being a pirate just like my old man.
But did I actually become a real one, leaving everyone behind to do so?
Why am I here?
Why am I here with these humans?
The only ones I've ever trusted were Dr. Herilook and Dr. Eam.
Even among my fellow reindeer, I had no friends.
I was always alone.
I promise I'm not going to shoot you, see?
Listen, my name is Herilook!
Dr. Herilook!
And if that's true, there's no disease that can't be cured.
Let them all laugh at me.
I don't care.
My medical skills will save this country yet, you'll see.
I raised this skull and crossbones to challenge all diseases of the world.
A skull?
This symbol represents my conviction and belief that there is nothing that's impossible.
I will save this country with my doctor's skills.
And now I have friends?
Six of them?
How am I supposed to believe I'm out here with them as a doctor on a pirate ship?
But what if it's true?
None of that's going to happen.
Nothing can take away my dreams.
And I know it's the same for you guys, too.
Here, here, here.
Here.
Here, here.
Nami, Zoro, sit tight and don't worry, we're coming for you.
Hey, wake up!
We're already up and ready.
Mr. Cook and Mr. Doctor are here too.
There's no way I'd ever leave a lady like that behind.
And besides, Robin's gonna need herself a bodyguard.
And if anyone gets injured, then they'll surely need the assistance of a doctor, right?
Which means that I should stay behind and guard the ship.
You're coming too, Usopp.
Well, actually, I've got this.
My heart'll stop if I go on the island disease.
Just come with us.
I know one thing.
Usopp, the brave warrior of the sea, is a man who always comes through when things get rough.
That's me.
All right then, we're all going!
Oh, crap.
I got caught up in the moment.
So, how are we gonna get across the bay to the island?
I think a raft is the most viable option.
Good idea.
Hey, make us a raft, Usopp.
Why should I?
I'm Captain Usopp, remember?
Yeah, yeah.
At the very least, I'm a sniper.
Either way, I can't properly do the job of a shipwright.
To make a raft, all you do is tie some locks together.
Problem solved.
Are you sure those are the right kinds of knots to use?
Well, yeah.
A knot's a knot, right?
You've gotta be kidding.
That thing's gonna break apart as soon as it hits the water.
But mine looks a whole lot cooler.
Check this baby out.
No way.
Mine is the coolest.
Sorry, but there's no comparison.
Mine rules.
Oh, come on.
Seriously?
How can you call yourselves pirates when you can't even make a decent raft?
Such amazing workmanship.
See?
Usopp's a man who always comes through.
Wait.
How do I know how to build this thing?
I don't get it.
All right.
Let's go!
Thanks for the room.
What do I owe you?
Uh, sorry.
Who are you?
Huh?
What?
I'm a guest of the inn.
I stayed here last night.
Do you recognize her?
No, I've never seen her before.
Uh...
Wait.
She might be a thief.
What?
A thief?
Hey, now hold on a second.
I'm a customer.
I just met all three of you yesterday.
Do you seriously not remember me?
I mean, surely you do, Mr. Manager.
Manager?
You mean me?
Uh, he is the manager of this inn, right?
I don't know.
Huh?
It's nice that I got to stay for free and all, but what in the world is going on here?
Could this mean that...
Who are you?
Don't tell me you've lost your memories, too.
It's just like what happened to me yesterday.
Yesterday?
Yeah, that's right.
They might have come through here.
There was a swordsman with green hair and a woman driving a weird boat.
So did you see him?
Yesterday.
Now, what did I do yesterday?
Ah, not you two!
What is wrong with the people on this crazy island?
Not a single one of these nitwits remembers anything about what they did yesterday!
What carefree people?
I think it's a little more than being carefree.
And we're not really ones to talk.
Huh?
We're just like them.
It might be more than just coincidence.
So what's the plan?
What do we do?
It'll be kind of tough finding them in this situation.
Right!
Back to the ship, then!
No good thing is going to come from us wandering around on this creepy island.
So, what do you say?
Hey, Nami!
Oh, crap!
Hey!
Wait!
Ah!
What a day.
Why'd you run away from us, Nami?
You'll never get this away from me, got it?
You'd have to kill me before I'd let it go.
Don't say that.
There's no way I'd hurt a beautiful lady like you.
That's ridiculous.
I promise I won't lay a finger on you.
Though I'd really like to.
Hey, Doc, what kind of disease does he have?
Can't you do anything for him?
It's definitely a serious condition, but I'm pretty sure there's no cure.
Fine.
Let's make a deal.
What kind of deal?
I promise to give you 10% of my treasure if you promise to take me back to Kokoyashi Village.
No way.
Okay, then 20%.
Nuh-uh.
Fine, 30%.
Can't do it.
It'll kill me, but 50%.
Sorry.
Just how much of this treasure are you trying to swindle me out of?
Come on, Nami, you love that treasure.
There's no way you'd ever give it up to anybody.
Hey, how the heck did you know that I was going to double cross you?
Because we're friends, Nami.
How else?
Give me a break.
Why would I ever be friends with the likes of you?
This is ridiculous.
The negotiations are over.
I'm leaving.
See ya.
Step aside, please.
Not happening.
Nami, you are going to come along with us.
You're out of your freaking mind.
Why would I go anywhere with you guys?
Now move it, jerk!
I won't.
Miss Navigator.
Huh?
You've been feeling that there's something odd about this island ever since you set foot on it.
Am I wrong?
You look perplexed.
What's the matter?
There was a boy holding a strange horn.
Yeah, last night I got a good punch in on him.
And then some smoke came out of his horn and then it went into my body and then I could remember stuff.
That's right.
The captain has all of his memories back.
Preposterous.
Are you sure you weren't dreaming?
No, it's true.
I saw the whole thing happen with my own two eyes.
I also seem to remember seeing that little brat the night before last as well.
What I want to know is why he came back.
It's just a theory, but maybe he wasn't able to steal all of your memories in one shot.
Even with just what I know, you all seem to have experienced numerous incredible adventures during your journeys together.
It was too much to take all at once, so he starved himself and returned yesterday?
The theory seems logical enough.
Hey, Robin, do you think that memories taste good?
So then, that little boy...
Bye!
See ya!
All right then!
Let's go kick that little runt's butt again and get everybody's memories back!
Then Zoro will rejoin our crew!
I doubt that it's going to be as simple as that, but we definitely need to give that brat some painful payback.
Look, can't we just forget about Zoro?
Zoro, even if we get our memories back, it's kind of unsettling to be in a pirate crew on a pirate ship with a pirate hunter, you know?
Zoro's the swordsman and Nami's the navigator.
They're our friends and part of our crew!
It still bothers me when you say that, you know!
How can I be a pirate, much less friends with pirates?
Look, I'm the one who's going to be bothered without you.
Without a navigator, the ship can't go anywhere, understand?
Robin, do you have any idea where that little runt is hiding?
Well, there is one place that I'd like to check out.
Okay then, let's go!
Hey, wait, Michael!
Don't worry, I'll carry the lady's stuff!
If doing so means I get to be with you, then this is no trouble at all!
Eh, got a bad feeling about this.
Even with everything that's happening, they all follow Luffy.
I wonder if it's true that I have friends now.
Hey, Chopper, what are you waiting for?
Let's go!
Aye, aye!
If you want to eat, help yourself.
Well, it's true that I am rather hungry, but this isn't the kind of food that I eat.
Oh, yeah?
Tell me, why haven't you asked me who I am yet?
Ah, that's right.
The people that live on this island don't remember anything.
Not even their own names, huh?
No point in asking.
You're on a quest to become the strongest in the world, right?
Hmm.
If that's the case, then I think that Monkey D. Luffy would be the perfect opponent for you.
Hi, I'm Luffy!
So what's your name?
Talking about that idiot in the straw hat?
I'm actually surprised that someone like Roro Noah Zoro couldn't see that man's strength.
See his strength?
What do you mean?
I mean that Monkey D. Luffy destroyed the vicious Arlong along with his fishmen pirate crew in the East Blue.
Then in the Grand Line, he managed to bring down Crocodile, one of the seven warlords of the sea, all by himself.
Warlords of the sea?
Yeah, and that's not all.
On the Sky Islands, he beat up a powerful god named Eneru.
And after that, he went on a rampage in a marine base.
Against Luffy, even the marines had to throw in the towel.
I've never seen another pirate like him.
Don't screw with me.
I'm not in the mood for any more of these cock and bull stories, you got it?
So, after hearing all that, you want to fight Luffy, don't you?
What are you doing?
Where are we?
Is this where that weird kid lives?
This place is giving me the creeps!
Did I catch a cold or something?
I've been shivering for a while now.
If only we had a doctor here.
Wait, that's me!
I bet these pirates are trying to take me out to the middle of nowhere so they can steal my gold!
I won't let them do it!
Nami's been shooting glances at me this whole time!
That can only mean one thing!
She's fallen in love with me!
Back at ya!
Is that some kind of signal that he's about to steal my gold?
He's freaking me out!
Now I see.
Butterfly!
What's up, Robin?
Did you find something?
I just determined the culprit that stole your memories.
Consequently, it's not the one we thought it was.
Wait a second.
You mean it's not that little brat?
Now, let's make our way to the Sea God's Palace.
Sea God's Palace?
Okay, but why?
Just a hunch.
Let's make our way to the Sea God's Palace.
One piece Zorro bears his fangs savage animal stands in the way